=== MISSING QUESTION TRANSLATIONS (0) ===

=== MISSING OPTION TRANSLATIONS (647) ===
$
1 million
1.2 million
10
100,000
105
11
12
120
13
15
150
1534
16
17
1756
1774
1791
18
1807
19
1900
1901
1915
1916
1917
1918
1919
1920
1921
1923
1925
1963
1965
1969
1971
1975
1975 and 1980
1980
1980 and 1995
1988
1992
1994
1995
1995 and 2000
1996
2
20
2006
21
25
3
30
308
338
350
4
400
400,000
5
500,000
600,000
7
700,000
8
800,000
9
900,000
96
A cultural event
A highway
A leader of responsible government
A military court
A military event
A military government
A military meeting
A mining operation
A mountain range
A municipal court
A provincial court
A river
A secret railway
A system where the President has all power
A system where the monarch has unlimited power
A system without elections
A tax on all immigrants
A tax on exports
A tax on imports
A trade dispute
A trade meeting
A transportation system
A type of beaver
A type of maple tree
A war hero
A war with USA
Aboriginal, French, British, and other groups
Act
Alaska Highway
Alexander Graham Bell
Alexander Mackenzie
Alice Munro
All are the same
All are the same size
All eastern provinces
All northern regions
All of them
All opposition parties
All power in one government
All provinces
All provinces and territories
All residents
Always Conservative
Always Liberal
Always Parti QuΘbΘcois
Americans
Americans invaded
An artist
An explorer
Any language
Anyone with a SIN number
Appalachian Mountains
Arctic Circle
Arctic territories
Artists
Arviat
Atlantic Canada
Atlantic Region
Atlantic Region, Central Canada, Prairie Region, West Coast, Northern Territories
Atlantic, Central, Prairie, West Coast, North
August 1
BC
BC, Alberta
Baker Lake
Ballot numbers
Banff National Park
Beginning of Confederation
Bill
Blue and white
Both La Fontaine and Baldwin
Both Nobel Prize and Order of Canada
Both Quebec and Ontario
Both party and candidate names
Brandon
Brian Mulroney
British in 1763
Budget
C$
CAD
CETA
CPTPP
Canada European Trade Alliance
Canada Pacific Trade Partnership Program
Canada Parks
Canada the Beautiful
Canada's greatest soldier
Canada, Mexico, UK
Canada, USA, Mexico
Canada, USA, UK
Canada-Greenland border
Canada-Mexico border
Canada-US border
Canadian Broadcasting Channel
Canadian Broadcasting Company
Canadian Business Corporation
Canadian Dollar
Canadian Euro
Canadian European Trade Agreement
Canadian Museum of History, Museum of Civilization, National Gallery
Canadian National Parks
Canadian Pacific Trade Partnership
Canadian Peso
Canadian Pound
Canadian Shield
Canadian citizens
Canadian citizens 18 years or older
Canadians in 1867
Candidate names
Candidate names and party affiliations
Caribou
Central Canada
Central Canada, Prairie Region, North
Central government
Charter of Rights and Freedoms
Chief Justice
Citizenship ceremony
Coalition government
Coast Mountains
Committee review
Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement
Constitution only
Continental Economic Trade Agreement
Continental Pacific Trade Partnership
Corner Brook
Cornwall
Court of Appeal
Cured diabetes
Curling
Dartmouth
David Thompson
Dawson City
December 11
December 31, 1867
Democracy, Republic, Federalism
Diamonds, gold, zinc
Dieppe
Division of power between federal and provincial governments
Drafting Confederation principles
East, Central, West, North, South
East, West, North
East, West, North, South, Central
Education
Elect representatives
Elected government
End of Seven Years' War and cession of New France to Britain
End of World War I
End of a war
Enforce laws
English only
English, French, and Indigenous languages
Equal pay for equal work
Established border in the east
Established border in the west
Every 3 years
Everyone is guilty until proven innocent
Everyone is innocent until proven guilty
Existence of different cultures and ethnicities in a society
Explorers
Famous Canadian artists
Famous Canadian landscape painters
Famous Canadian thinkers and scholars
Famous politicians
Federal Court
Federal government
Federalism, Parliamentary democracy, Constitutional monarchy
First Confederation conference
First reading
Fishing
Five
Five Fathers of Confederation
Five explorers
Five large lakes between Canada and the United States
Five military heroes
Five women who fought for women's right to vote
Flag, Anthem
Foreign policy
Forestry, energy, pulp and paper
Fort Smith
Four
Fraser River
Frederick Banting and Charles Best
Freedom Tower
Freedom from taxes, Freedom from military service, Freedom from jury duty
Freedom from taxes, military service, jury duty
Freedom of conscience and religion, Freedom of thought, belief, opinion and expression, Freedom of peaceful assembly, Freedom of association
Freedom of conscience and religion, thought, expression, peaceful assembly and association
Freedom of movement, work, education, health
Freedom of speech, press, religion, assembly
Freedom to work, Freedom to travel, Freedom to vote, Freedom to own property
French defeated British
French in 1763
French only
French, British, American
Fruit orchards and vineyards
Full constitutional independence from Britain
Fur trade
Fur trading
GATT
Gabriel Dumont
Gander
Gatineau
General Andrew McNaughton
General Arthur Currie
General Guy Simonds
General Harry Crerar
General Sam Hughes
Getting a job, Taking care of one's family, Working hard
God Save the Queen
God save the Queen, long live the King
Gold, lead, zinc
Gold, silver, copper
Government policy only
Government responsible to the Queen
Government responsible to the people
Government responsible to the people through Parliament
Government that makes good decisions
Government that must be accountable to Parliament
Government with less than 50% of seats
Government with majority of seats
Government with many responsibilities
Governor General
Governor Simcoe
Great Bear Lake
Great Lakes
Great Slave Lake
Guglielmo Marconi
Haines Junction
Halifax, Fredericton, Charlottetown, St. John's
Halifax, St. John's
Hamilton
Hay River
Health care
Henry Hudson
Highway 401
House, Senate, Courts
Independence of Canada
Interpret and apply laws
Inuvik
It ended World War I
It had no significance
It was Canada's first major victory as an independent nation
It was a draw
It was the largest battle
It's always dark
It's very hot
James Cook
James Naismith
January 1, 1867
January 11
Jasper National Park
Jean ChrΘtien
Jean Talon
John A. Macdonald
July 1
July 1, 1867
July 4, 1867
June 1
Lake Athabasca
Lake Winnipeg
Lakes in the Arctic
Lakes in the Canadian Shield
Lakes in the Rocky Mountains
Largest strike in Canadian history
Laurentian Mountains
Laurentian Plateau
Laval
Legal system based on judicial precedent
Legal system based on judicial precedent (in all provinces except Quebec)
Legal system based on written laws
Legal system based on written laws (in Quebec)
Legislation
Legislative process
Lester B. Pearson
Lethbridge
Lieutenant Governor
London
Lord Durham
Lord Elgin
Louis Riel
Louis de Frontenac
Louis-Hippolyte La Fontaine
Lucy Maud Montgomery
Mackenzie River
Make laws
Making laws
Manitoba, Saskatchewan
Manitoba, Saskatchewan, Alberta
Maple leaf, Beaver
Maple leaf, Flag
Margaret Atwood
Maritime provinces only
Maritime, Central, Prairie, Pacific, Arctic
Maritime, Ontario, Quebec, Prairies, BC
Marshall McLuhan
Mayor
Men and women are equal under the law
Michigan, Erie, Ontario, Superior, Great Bear
Military law
Military rule
Mining
Mining, manufacturing, technology
Monarchy, Dictatorship, Federalism
Moncton
Monetary policy
Moose
Moose Jaw
More than 600,000
Mount Fairweather
Mount Logan
Mount Pearl
Mount Robson
Mount Waddington
Municipal
National American Free Trade Agreement
National Gallery
National Parks Service
National defence, foreign policy, citizenship
National government
Natural resources
Naturalization ceremony
New American Free Trade Agreement
Nikola Tesla
No award
No cultures
No equality
No government
No languages
No legal system
No national museums
No such rights exist
No, never
No, voting is secret
Nobel Prize in Medicine
None
None of them
North Atlantic Free Trade Agreement
Northern Canada
Northern Territories
Not yet
Nova Scotia (Halifax), New Brunswick (Fredericton), PEI (Charlottetown), Newfoundland and Labrador (St. John's)
Nova Scotia, New Brunswick, PEI, Newfoundland and Labrador
Nova Scotia, New Brunswick, Prince Edward Island, Newfoundland and Labrador
Nova Scotia, PEI
November 1
November 11
O Canada! Our home and native land! True patriot love in all of us command
O Canada, land of the free, home of the brave
Oath ceremony
Obeying laws, Respecting others
Obeying the law
Official Languages Act
Oil and gas
Oil production
Oil, gas, coal
One
Only Aboriginal peoples
Only Nova Scotia and New Brunswick
Only Yukon and NWT
Only as observer
Only candidate names
Only for citizens
Only for some people
Only in 1995
Only in writing
Only numbers
Only one culture
Only one museum
Only provincial museums
Only through a lawyer
Only to family
Only to officials
Ontario only
Ontario, Quebec
Ontario, Quebec, Territories
Opening Address
Ottawa River
Over 1000
Over 1500
Over 35,000
Over 40,000
Over 45,000
Over 50
Over 50,000
Over 500
Over 60
Over 60,000
Over 70
Over 70,000
Over 750
Over 80
Parliament
Parliamentary process
Party names
Party names only
Paying taxes, Voting, Serving on jury
People over 54
People over 54 and under 18
People over 55
People over 55 and under 18
People over 60 and under 16
People over 65
People over 65 and under 18
People under 18
Permanent residents
Pierre Elliott Trudeau
Pioneers in communication theory
Polar Bear
Police, fire services, libraries
Politicians
Potatoes and Anne of Green Gables
Prairie
Prairie Provinces
Prairie Region
Premier
Prime Minister
Prime Minister, Parliament, Supreme Court
Prime Minister, Premier, Mayor
Prince Albert
Provincial
Provincial Court
Quebec Act of 1774
Quebec only
Quebec, Ontario
Rankin Inlet
Recognition and respect for different cultures
Red Deer
Red and gold
Red, white, and blue
Rick Hansen
Right to work anywhere
Rights of each person as an individual
Rights of groups
Rights of groups such as Aboriginal peoples
Rights of individuals only
Rights of the government
Robert Baldwin
Robertson Davies
Rocky Mountains
Royal Address
Royal Assent
Royal Canadian Maritime Police
Royal Canadian Military Police
Royal Canadian Municipal Police
Saint John
Same opportunities and responsibilities
Saskatoon
Saved millions of lives worldwide
September 1
Seven Fathers of Confederation
Seven military heroes
Seven provinces
Seven territories
Simon Fraser
Sir John A. Macdonald
Sir Louis-Hippolyte La Fontaine
Six
Some people are presumed guilty
Some people have more rights
St. Lawrence River
State of the Union
Statute
Steinbach
Stratford
Study in Canada
Studying
Summerside
Superior, Huron, Erie, Ontario, Winnipeg
Superior, Huron, Michigan, Erie, Ontario
Supreme Court Building
Supreme Court of Canada
Swearing-in ceremony
Sydney
Taking responsibility for oneself and family
Temporary government
Terrorist crisis in Quebec
Terry Fox
The Bill of Rights
The Breadbasket of Canada
The Charter of Rights and Freedoms
The Chief Justice
The Constitution
The Gateway
The Governor General
The Heartland
The Keystone
The Magna Carta
The Maple Leaf
The Maple Leaf Forever
The Mayor
The Premier
The Province of a Thousand Lakes
The Red Ensign
The Stars and Stripes
The Union Jack
The White House
The beaver
The border between Canada and USA from ocean to Great Lakes
The candidate's name
The creation of Canadian Confederation
The flag
The governing party
The highest court in Canada
The independence of Canada
The largest party
The maple leaf
The moose
The party chosen by the Governor General
The party chosen by the PM
The party name
The party with the most seats
The party with the most seats in the House of Commons
The party with the most votes
The party with the second most seats
The party with the second-largest number of seats in the House of Commons
The person elected in your riding
The sun doesn't set in summer
There are many sunny days
They are each other's largest trading partners
They cooperate on many issues
They have the same government system
They share the world's longest undefended border
Third reading
This changes with elections
This varies by location
Thomas Edison
Thompson
Three
Throne Speech
To be loyal to Canada
To elect representatives
To fulfill their duties as citizens
To implement and enforce laws (Prime Minister and Cabinet)
To interpret laws
To lead the government
To make laws
To obey the law
To represent the Crown in Canada
Tommy Douglas
Toronto, Montreal, Vancouver
Toronto, Quebec City
Tourists
Trans-Canada Highway
Traveling
Truro
Two
US-Mexico border
USA, Mexico, UK
USMCA/CUSMA
Unity Tower
Uprisings in Upper and Lower Canada
Use of many languages
Use of one language
Use of two languages (English and French)
Victoria
Victoria, Edmonton
Victory Tower
Visit Canada
Volunteering
Vote in federal elections
Voting in elections
War heroes
Waterton Lakes National Park
Watson Lake
Wayne Gretzky
West Coast
Western Canada
Whitehorse, Yellowknife, Iqaluit
Wilfrid Laurier
William Lyon Mackenzie King
Winnipeg, Regina
Won Nobel Prize
Work in Canada
Working
Yellowhead Highway
Yes, always
Yes, you have the right
Yoho National Park
Yukon (Whitehorse), Northwest Territories (Yellowknife), Nunavut (Iqaluit)

=== MISSING EXPLANATION TRANSLATIONS (191) ===
24 Sussex Drive is the official residence of the Prime Minister of Canada.
A bill goes through the legislative process in Parliament and receives Royal Ass...
A constitutional monarchy is a system where the King/Queen is head of state but ...
A federal election ballot contains the names of candidates running in your ridin...
A jury is a group of citizens who make decisions in court.
A parliamentary democracy is a system of government where Parliament is the prim...
Alberta is known for its oil and gas industry and the Rocky Mountains.
Alexander Graham Bell invented the telephone, though it was patented in the USA.
Alexander Mackenzie was the first European to reach the Pacific Ocean by land in...
Approximately 600,000 Canadians served in World War I.
Banff National Park, established in 1885, was the first national park in Canada.
Bilingualism is the use of two languages (English and French).
British Columbia is on the Pacific coast and known for mountains and nature.
CBC stands for Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, the national broadcaster.
CETA stands for Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement between Canada and th...
CPTPP includes 11 countries.
CPTPP stands for Comprehensive and Progressive Agreement for Trans-Pacific Partn...
Canada Day is celebrated on July 1st to commemorate the anniversary of Confedera...
Canada and the USA have different government systems, though they share many sim...
Canada became a country on July 1, 1867, with the British North America Act, whi...
Canada has 10 provinces and 3 territories.
Canada has 10 provinces: Alberta, British Columbia, Manitoba, New Brunswick, New...
Canada has 3 territories: Yukon, Northwest Territories, and Nunavut.
Canada has two national sports: hockey (winter) and lacrosse (summer).
Canada has two official languages: English and French.
Canada is a member of G20 (Group of Twenty), which includes the world's largest ...
Canada is a member of G7 (Group of Seven), which includes advanced industrial co...
Canada is a member of La Francophonie, an international organization of French-s...
Canada is a member of NATO (North Atlantic Treaty Organization).
Canada is a member of the Commonwealth of Nations.
Canada is a member of the United Nations (UN).
Canada's maple leaf flag was adopted in 1965.
Canada's national museums include Canadian Museum of History, Museum of Civiliza...
Canadarm is a robotic arm developed for the space shuttle, a significant Canadia...
Canadian citizens who are 18 years or older may be called to serve on a jury.
Charlottetown is the capital city of Prince Edward Island.
Civil Law is a legal system based on written laws, used in Quebec.
Collective rights are rights of groups such as Aboriginal peoples.
Common Law is a legal system based on judicial precedent, used in all provinces ...
Cultural diversity is the existence of different cultures and ethnicities in a s...
David Thompson was a great surveyor and explorer who mapped much of western Cana...
Edmonton is the capital city of Alberta.
English and French are the two official languages of Canada.
Equality means all individuals have equal rights and opportunities.
Federal elections must be held at least every 5 years, but can be called earlier...
Federalism is the division of power between federal and provincial governments.
Four original provinces joined Confederation in 1867: Ontario, Quebec, Nova Scot...
Frederick Banting and Charles Best discovered insulin in 1921, a major medical b...
Frederick Banting and Charles Best won the Nobel Prize in Medicine for discoveri...
Fredericton is the capital city of New Brunswick.
General Andrew McNaughton was the commander of Canadian forces in World War II.
General Arthur Currie was the commander of Canadian forces in World War I.
Great Bear Lake is the largest lake entirely within Canada.
Halifax is the capital city of Nova Scotia.
His Majesty's Loyal Opposition is the party with the second-largest number of se...
Hockey is the national winter sport and lacrosse is the national summer sport of...
In Canada, voting is secret and you are not obliged to tell anyone how you voted...
In Canada, you have the right to question the police about their service or cond...
In the Oath of Citizenship, new citizens promise to be loyal to Canada, obey the...
Individual rights are rights of each person as an individual.
Insulin was discovered in 1921 by Frederick Banting and Charles Best.
Iqaluit is the capital city of Nunavut.
Jacques Cartier arrived in Canada in 1534, making him one of the first European ...
Jacques Cartier was the first European to arrive in Canada in 1534.
Lester B. Pearson won the Nobel Peace Prize and served as Prime Minister from 19...
Lucy Maud Montgomery wrote 'Anne of Green Gables'.
Manitoba is known as the 'Province of a Thousand Lakes' and is the geographic ce...
Many early Canadian companies engaged in fur trading, mining, and fishing.
Many early Canadian companies engaged in the fur trade, fishing, and mining indu...
Marshall McLuhan and Harold Innis were pioneers in communication theory.
Mobility rights allow Canadian citizens to enter and leave Canada freely, and to...
Mount Logan in Yukon is the highest mountain in Canada.
Multiculturalism is the recognition and respect for different cultures.
NAFTA stands for North American Free Trade Agreement, implemented in 1994 betwee...
NAFTA was between Canada, USA, and Mexico.
NAFTA was implemented in 1994.
Nellie McClung was a women's rights activist and one of the 'Famous Five'.
New Brunswick is the only officially bilingual province in Canada.
New citizens take the Oath of Citizenship at a citizenship ceremony.
Newfoundland and Labrador is the youngest province (joined in 1949), known for c...
Newfoundland and Labrador joined Canada in 1949, making it the youngest province...
Northwest Territories has diamonds, gold, and zinc mining.
Nova Scotia is known as 'Canada's Ocean Playground'.
Nunavut is the largest and youngest territory (created in 1999), with a majority...
Nunavut was created in 1999, making it the youngest and largest territory.
O Canada is the national anthem of Canada.
O Canada was officially adopted as the national anthem in 1980.
Ontario is the most populous province in Canada, home to Canada's capital (Ottaw...
Over 1 million Canadians served in World War II.
Over 1000 National Historic Sites are registered in Canada.
Over 45,000 Canadians were killed in World War II.
Over 60,000 Canadians were killed in World War I.
Over 70 treaties exist between the Canadian government and First Nations.
Parks Canada manages the national park system in Canada.
Parliament Hill in Ottawa is where the Parliament of Canada meets.
People over 54 and under 18 are exempt from the citizenship test.
Pierre Elliott Trudeau served as Prime Minister from 1968-1979 and 1980-1984.
Prince Edward Island is famous for potatoes and Anne of Green Gables.
Prince Edward Island is the smallest province in Canada, known for potatoes and ...
Prince Edward Island is the smallest province in Canada.
Provincial governments are responsible for education, health care, and natural r...
Quebec City is the capital city of Quebec.
Quebec independence referendums were held in 1980 and 1995.
Quebec is the largest province in Canada by area.
Quebec is the only province with French as the official language, and it is the ...
Quebec's economy today includes forestry, energy, pulp and paper, mining, manufa...
RCMP stands for Royal Canadian Mounted Police, the federal police force.
Regina is the capital city of Saskatchewan.
Responsible government means a government that must be accountable to Parliament...
Rideau Hall in Ottawa is the official residence of the Governor General.
Samuel de Champlain founded Quebec City in 1608.
Saskatchewan is known as the 'Breadbasket of Canada' and is the largest wheat pr...
Saskatchewan is known as the 'Breadbasket of Canada' because it is the largest w...
Sir John A. Macdonald was Canada's first Prime Minister, serving from 1867-1873 ...
Sir Louis-Hippolyte La Fontaine and Robert Baldwin were the first leaders of a r...
St. John's is the capital city of Newfoundland and Labrador.
The 'Famous Five' were five women who fought for women's right to vote in the Su...
The 'Group of Seven' were famous Canadian landscape painters.
The 49th Parallel is the border between Canada and USA from ocean to Great Lakes...
The Atlantic Region includes Nova Scotia (Halifax), New Brunswick (Fredericton),...
The Bank of Canada is responsible for monetary policy.
The Battle of Vimy Ridge in 1917 was Canada's first major victory as an independ...
The Battle of Vimy Ridge took place in 1917 and was an important Canadian victor...
The British North America Act (1867) created the Canadian Confederation.
The Canada Act (1982) achieved full constitutional independence from Britain.
The Canadian Charter of Rights and Freedoms contains Canada's fundamental rights...
The Canadian Charter of Rights and Freedoms was added to the Constitution in 198...
The Canadian Constitution was patriated in 1982, achieving full constitutional i...
The Canadian dollar can be represented as $, C$, or CAD.
The Canadian dollar is the currency used in Canada.
The Canadian flag has red and white colors with a red maple leaf in the center.
The Canadian flag is called the Maple Leaf or l'UnifoliΘ.
The Charlottetown Conference (1864) was the first Confederation conference.
The Charter of Rights and Freedoms was incorporated into the Canadian Constituti...
The Executive branch (Prime Minister and Cabinet) implements and enforces laws.
The Governor General is appointed by the King or Queen on the advice of the Prim...
The Governor General represents the Crown (monarch) in Canada.
The Great Lakes are five large lakes located between Canada and the United State...
The Head Tax was a discriminatory tax charged to Chinese immigrants to Canada, s...
The House of Commons has 338 members, elected by Canadians in federal elections.
The King or Queen (monarch) is Canada's head of state.
The Mackenzie River is the longest river in Canada.
The Multiculturalism Act was passed in 1988, recognizing cultural diversity.
The October Crisis (1970) was a terrorist crisis in Quebec.
The Official Languages Act was passed in 1969, guaranteeing the use of English a...
The Oregon Treaty (1846) established the border in the west between Canada and U...
The Peace Tower is the iconic tower on Parliament Hill.
The Prairie Region includes Manitoba, Saskatchewan, and Alberta.
The Prime Minister is Canada's head of government.
The Quebec Conference (1864) was for drafting Confederation principles.
The Rebellions of 1837 were uprisings in Upper and Lower Canada.
The Senate has 105 senators, appointed by the Governor General on the advice of ...
The Speech from the Throne marks the opening of each session of Parliament.
The Speech from the Throne outlines the government's plans for the upcoming sess...
The St. Lawrence River flows through both Quebec and Ontario.
The Supreme Court of Canada has 9 judges.
The Supreme Court of Canada is the highest court in Canada.
The Trans-Canada Highway is the longest highway in Canada, stretching from coast...
The Treaty of Ghent (1814) established the border in the east between Canada and...
The Treaty of Paris (1763) ended the Seven Years' War and ceded New France to Br...
The Treaty of Paris was signed in 1763, ending the Seven Years' War and ceding N...
The Winnipeg General Strike (1919) was the largest strike in Canadian history.
The beaver is the national animal of Canada.
The border between Canada and the United States is the longest undefended border...
The capital city varies depending on which province or territory you live in.
The citizenship test can be taken in English or French.
The citizenship test consists of 20 questions.
The citizenship test duration is 45 minutes.
The current Canadian flag with the maple leaf was adopted in 1965.
The five Great Lakes are: Lake Superior, Lake Huron, Lake Michigan, Lake Erie, a...
The five regions of Canada are: Atlantic Region, Central Canada, Prairie Region,...
The four fundamental freedoms are: freedom of conscience and religion, freedom o...
The government of all of Canada is called the federal government.
The multiculturalism policy was adopted in 1971.
The territories are Yukon (Whitehorse), Northwest Territories (Yellowknife), and...
The three branches of government are: Executive (Prime Minister and Cabinet), Le...
The three levels of government in Canada are: Federal, Provincial, and Municipal...
There are 17 UNESCO World Heritage Sites in Canada.
There are five Great Lakes: Superior, Huron, Michigan, Erie, and Ontario.
To pass the citizenship test, you must answer at least 15 questions correctly (7...
Tommy Douglas is known as the 'Father of Canadian Medicare'.
Toronto is the capital city of Ontario.
USMCA/CUSMA (New North American Free Trade Agreement) replaced NAFTA in 2020.
Victoria is the capital city of British Columbia.
Whitehorse is the capital city of Yukon.
Wilfrid Laurier was the first French-Canadian Prime Minister, serving from 1896 ...
William Lyon Mackenzie King was Canada's longest-serving Prime Minister (1921-19...
Winnipeg is the capital city of Manitoba.
Yellowknife is the capital city of Northwest Territories.
Yukon is the only Canadian territory that shares a border with another country (...
Yukon is the smallest and westernmost territory, known for the Klondike Gold Rus...
