$5 bill
(Iqaluit )
(Multiple choice)
(See PDF)
01 July
1 million
10
10 provinces and 2 territories
12
1615
1632
1758
1776
1793
1840
1867
1880s
1885
1902
1905
1918
1949
1950
1960
1976
20
200,000
250 years
30%
338
4 years
63░)
7 years
7000.
9
96
99
A Bill.
A Chinese railroad worker
A Mari Usque Ad Mare
A New Law
A card that confirms that your name is on the voters list and states when and where you vote
A form that tells you when and where to vote.
A legal requirement
A military leader of the MΘtis in the 19th century
A person who represents all Canadians
A responsibility
Aboriginal Affairs
Aboriginal people of the arctic
About 240,000
About 34 million.
About 600,000
About every 4 years
Adult applicants 65 years of age and over
Alaska (Juneau) and Yukon Territory (Whitehorse)
Alberta
All answers correct
All of the Canadians living in the north
America
American Revolution f) Aboriginal peoples g) MΘtis h) Inuit
American and Indian
American railroad engineers
Americans
An effort by women to work
An ôXö
Any Canadian citizen who is at least 18 years old.
Appointed by the Prime Minister
April 1st, 1999
Army
Asia
Atlantic, Arctic and Pacific
Austria
Band chiefs and councilors
Band chiefs and councilors.
Beaver
Because she has a university degree
Being able to live and work anywhere in Canada
Being the same
Benevolent dictatorship
BlackBerry
British Columbia
British Government
Buying a house and a TV.
By arbitrary actions
By the Governor General of Canada
Call Elections Canada or visit their website.
Canada enjoys close relations with the United States
Canada freely CanadaÆs Economy/ CanadaÆs Regions Pages 42 & 45
Canada, Mexico and the United States.
CanadaÆs first Prime minister
CanadaÆs greatest soldier in the First World War.
Canadian citizen, 18 years or older and on the list of electors
Canadian citizens
Canadian victory in World War II
Canadians The Canadian Charter of Rights and Freedoms
Canadians The Canadian Charter of Rights and Freedoms.
Canadians have freedom of speech
Catholic
Central Canada
Chinese railroad workers
Citizenship and highways
Civil Rights
Commissioner
Communications, retail services
Conservative (Scheer ,) NDP (Jagmeet Singh ,) Liberal (Trudeau ) Bloc Quebecois (Ouellete ) Green Party (May)
Constitution 1982
Currency
David Johnston
Daylight can last up to 24 hours in fall
Defence
Dr, John
Dr. Emily Stowe
Education
Education and health care
Elected by Canadian citizens.
Emile Nelligan, Marshall Mcluhan, Chantal Petitclerc
Emily Carr
England & United States
English as first language
English common law
Equal rights for men and women
Ernie Eves
Europe
Everyone is innocent until proven guilty
Executive, Police and Judicial
Fathers of confederation
Federal
Federal and provincial
Federal, provincial, county
Federal, provincial, or territorial and local elections
Fighter Planes
First Nations, MΘtis and Inuit
Five
Focus on citizenship and allegiance, be a symbol of Canadian sovereignty and guardian of constitutional freedoms
Founder of the city of Victoria
France
Fraser River
Free trade between Canada, USA and Mexico
Freedom of conscience and religion
Freedom of thought, belief, opinion, and expression
Freedom to buy a house and freedom of religion
Freedoms
Freedoms ).
Freedoms.
French Culture
French as first language
French, American and Indian
From sea to sea
From sea to sea.
From the Inuit word meaning country
General.
Geopolitical entity
Gerhard Herzberg
Get a job, make money, raise a family, pay taxes, mow your lawn, vote
God Save the Queen (King.)
God Save the Queen or King
Government Responsibilities
Government.
Governor General of Canada
Governor General of Canada.
Great Britain
Green Party
Health
Health and Education
Her Majesty Queen Elizabeth II.
Highways
Hockey
In the Parliament of Canada
Insulin has saved 16 million lives worldwide.
Interprovincial trade and communications
It allows Canada to change the Constitution without asking approval of the British Government
It is a national summer sport
It was fourth-largest navy in world
Italian and French
Jagmeet Singh
James K. Bartleman
Jean Talon
Jewish
Jim Basally
John Cabot
Joining of communities to become a province
Joseph-Armand Bombardier
Justin Trudeau (Liberal Party)
Keep people safe and to enforce the law
King Charles II
Late 19th century
Learning to speak both official languages
Liberal Party
Liberal Party.
Lieutenant- Governor.
Lieutenant-Governor
Lord Durham
Louis Riel
Manitoba
Manitoba (Winnipeg) and Ontario (Regin
Manitoba, Saskatchewan and Alberta
Mathew Evans
Matters of national and international concern
May 21st when we celebrate the Queen's birthday
Mel Lastman
Men and women are equal under the law
Men and women are equal under the law.
Mexico
Midwest, North, South, East, Central
Mobility rights, Aboriginal PeopleÆs rights, and official language rights
Montreal- based traders who travelled by canoe
More than 600,000 Canadians served in the war
More than 600,000.
Music
MΘtis
National defense and foreign policy
National defense and foreign policy.
Natural Resources
Natural Resources and immigration
Natural resources
Natural resources, tourism and IT
Natural resources, tourism, and service industries
New Brunswick
New Brunswick, Nova Scotia, Alberta, Manitoba
New Democratic Party
Newfoundland
Newfoundland Labrador, Nova Scotia, New Brunswick and Prince Edward Island
Newfoundland and Labrador
No one
No one is
Northern Territories
Northwest Territories
Nova Scotia
Nova Scotia (Halifax), New Brunswick (Fredericton), Prince Edward Island (Charlottetown) and Quebec (Quebec City)
November 11th.
O Canada
O Canada! Our home and native land!
O Canada, we stand on guard for thee
Ontario
Ontario (Toronto) and Quebec (Quebec City.
Paris
Parliamentary government.
Paul Martin
Peace, Order and Good Government
Peace, Order and Good government
Peace, Order, and Good Government
People loyal to the Crown
People of Quebec
Phil Edwards
Police officers
Police state, parliamentary democracy and constitutional monarchy
Police, Senate and House of Commons
Prairie Provinces
Prairie provinces
Prairies
Premier
Premier, House of Commons and Senate
Prime Minister is called as the Premier
Prime Minister of Canada
Prince Edward Island
Provinces and Territorial government
Quebec
Raise funds for cancer research
Red and blue
Red and white
Reginald Fessenden
Reginald Fessenden, John Polanyi, Jean-Paul Riopelle
Rich in energy
Right to have a job, vote, drive, go to school
Roman Catholic
Ross Harper
Royal Canadian Mounted Police
Rule of law
Running the federal government departments
Saves the lives of people with heart disorder
Scotland and Ireland
Second
Serving on a jury
Sir Frederick Banting and Charles Best
Sir George- Etienne Cartier
Sir George- ╔tienne Cartier
Sir George-╔tienne Cartier
Sir John
Sir John Alexander MacDonald
Sir John Alexander Macdonald
Sir Leonard Tilley
Sir Louis-Hippolyte La Fontaine
Sir Sandford Fleming
Snow removal
South Canada
St. Lawrence River
Stanley Cup
Terry Fox
Thanksgiving Day
The 3rd Monday of October
The British Charter of Rights and Freedoms
The Canadian Charter of Rights and Freedoms
The Canadian Constitution and English common law
The Canadian Cross
The Confederation Act
The Conservative Party.
The Constitutional Act of 1791.
The Crown
The Crown contain symbols of England, France, Scotland and Ireland as well as red maple leaves
The East Movement
The Federal Court
The Governor General
The Governor General approves all bills and they become law after two debates
The Governor General of Canada
The Lieutenant Governor must approve the bill
The MLA
The Maple Leaf Forever
The New Democratic Party
The Northern Territories
The Pacific Ocean in the west
The Port of Vancouver
The Port of Vancouver, handles billions of dollars in goods traded around the world
The Prime Minister
The Province of Canada (Ontario and Quebec)
The Queen
The Queen appoints the Prime Minister
The Queen, House of Commons, Senate
The Queen, the House of Commons and the Senate.
The Quiet Revolution
The Quiet Revolution.
The Second Monday of October
The Sovereign
The Supreme Court of Canada
The United States Confederate soldiers came to Canada
The beaver
The birth of Canada
The caribou
The effort by women to achieve the right to vote
The effort by women to achieve the right to vote.
The first European settlers to arrive in Canada
The government must respect all of the legal rights a person is entitled to under the law
The greatest military leader of the MΘtis
The leader of the party with the most elected representatives becomes the Prime Minister
The official summer sport
The party with most elected representatives becomes the party in power
The party with the most elected representatives become the party in power. The Queen chooses the Prime Minister from this party
The party with the second most MPs.
The party with the second most MPÆs
The people" in the Inuktitut language
The police
The right to challenge unlawful detention by the state
The smallest country in world
They are chosen by the provincial premiers
They are selected by the Prime Minister
They share longest undefended border
Thomas Mulcair
Timber trade
To oppose or try to improve government proposals.
To remember our Sovereign, Queen Elizabeth II
To settle disputes.
Tolerated
Toronto
Trade with other countries changed the native way of life forever
True
Unity
Victoria Cross
Victoria Cross.
Vimy Day
Wayen Gretzky
White Shirt
Women achieved the right to vote
Yes, if you feel the need to.
Your employer
a) Alberta (Edmonton) and Saskatchewan (Toronto) b) Alberta (Edmonton) and Prince Edward Island (Charlottetown) c) Saskatchewan (Regina) and Manitoba (Winnipeg) Alberta (Edmonton) d) Saskatchewan (Regina), Manitoba (Winnipeg) and Ontario (Toronto)
a. India b. Japan c. China d. United States a. What types of jobs are provided by Natural resources industries? Agriculture, paper, food b. Mining, fishing, paper c. Fishing, agriculture, mining d. Food, paper, energy CanadaÆs History Pages 14-23
abilities.
accordance with the Constitution.
and Freedoms.
and give you the ballot to deposit in the box.
become the party in power.
brought about a fantastic victory
by the Prime Minister
communication company
community.
community. Volunteer
d) Ontario, Quebec, Nova Scotia and Newfoundland e) Ontario, Nova Scotia, New Brunswick and Alberta f) Ontario, Quebec, Prince Edward Island and Nova Scotia g) Nova Scotia, New Brunswick and the Province of Quebec
during the Second World War.
e) 1510 f) 1497 g) 1610 h) 1720
e) 1758 f) 1889 g) 1609 h) 1791
e) 1812 f) 1840 g) 1867 h) 1849
e) 1814 f) 1840 g) 1867 h) 1849
e) Acadia f) The ôProvince of Quebecö g) Quebec City h) Ontario
e) By the 1650s f) By the 1550s g) By the 1580s h) By the 1750s
e) From the Inuit word meaning country f) From the French word meaning joining g) From the MΘtis word meaning rivers h) From ôKanataö, the Huron-Iroquois word for village
e) Louis Riel f) Sir John
e) Ontario and New Brunswick f) Prince Edward Island and Quebec g) Ontario and Quebec h) Ontario and Prince Edward Island
e) Sir John
e) The Bloc Quebecois f) Conservative g) Liberal h) New Democratic
e) The HudsonÆs Bay Company f) The North Star company g) The Sears company h) The Trading Post Company
e) True f) False
e) United Kingdom and United States of America f) France and Canada g) United States of America, France and United Kingdom h) France and United Kingdom
election.
express ideas
f) The government is responsible for making laws g) The Crown must have the support of all of the elected representatives in order to govern h) The government must resign if it loses a confidence vote in the assembly
government
government in the Canada.
government in the Canadas
government in the Canadas.
her electoral district. This means she would be In the part of Montreal where she was elected.
i) Alberta (Edmonton) and Saskatchewan (Toronto) j) Alberta (Edmonton) and Prince Edward Island (Charlottetown) k) Saskatchewan (Regin
i) Central Canada j) Prairies k) Atlantic Canada l) Northern Canada
i) Dictatorship j) Parliamentary government k) Military Rule l) Communism
i) Midwest, North, South, East, Central j) Maritimes, Ontario, Quebec, Prairies, British Columbia k) Atlantic , Central, Prairie, West Coast and North l) West, Central, East, Prairies and Territories
i) New Brunswick j) Quebec k) Ontario l) Prince Edward Island
j) Federal, Provincial and City k) Federal, Territorial and Provincial l) Federal, State and Local
maintain distances
man Equality of women and men
of Freedoms).
of a Canadian
other rights or freedom of Aboriginal people
people The Constitutional Act of 1791.
provinces in 1604.
representative chamber . . .
representatives in order to govern.
respect the rights of others, eliminate injustice.
settle in Canada.
the West Coast
this is called a majority government.
this party becomes the Prime Minister.
ôCanada is a free country and home of the bravesö
